<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-03-02T13:34:39-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">John’s home page</title><subtitle>My home page</subtitle><author><name>John Boniello</name></author><entry><title type="html">My first project The Extended Time Calculator</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/03/02/First-Post.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My first project The Extended Time Calculator" /><published>2018-03-02T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-03-02T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/03/02/First-Post</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/03/02/First-Post.html">&lt;p&gt;My first project is up, it is called the Extended time calculator.  This project is in beta, if you have feedback please contact me and let me know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This project was inspired by my colleague Ann, who asked if it would be possible to create an app that helps teachers calculate the extended time a student with a disability may need. We orininally attempted this with excel, but could not figure out how to make it expandable and distribute it without the need for excel on a computer.  Also, people are uncomfortable with excel. I decided to take on the challenge and try to learn python again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has been about 5 years since I first tried to learn python.  Back then I didn’t have a project to work on or a reason to learn it.  I finally had a tangible project and decided I would give it a try.  After about 3 weeks and learning a lot about python, Qt, and packaging for windows, I now have a fully functioning program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately this only works on windows at the moment, but soon I hope to get it going on mac.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My ultimate goal is to make it a webapp, I’m thinking of using Django for that, but that requires even more learning!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>John Boniello</name></author><summary type="html">My first project is up, it is called the Extended time calculator. This project is in beta, if you have feedback please contact me and let me know.</summary></entry></feed>